<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Training and Placement Cell</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="aboutus">The Training and Placement Cell of the institute handles all aspects of placements at PU 
        for the students of all departments. It is a student body, directly under the supervision of the honourable Director,
        headed by the Training and Placement Officer and guided by the Faculty Advisers .The Cell stands for branding the
        outlook of the university to the corporate and the industry.
The Training and Placement Officer, Coordinators and the student representatives handle various crucial tasks in the Cell like
        reaching out to companies, scheduling and executing placement related activities and carrying out all official 
        communication with recruiters and students. The Cell strives to match recruiter expectations with students’ 
        aspirations. The team of student representatives coordinate the activities to ensure compliance with various institute 
        policies and company officials, who execute coordination with their recruiting organisations. Over the years the Cell
        has gone from strength to strength in 
        achieving outstanding placements at PU and will continue to do so in the years to come.</string>
    <string name="vacancy">vacancy</string>
    <string name="gpa">GPA</string>
    <array name="criteria">
        <item>Above 60%,Above 60%,Above 65%</item>
        <item>Above 55%,Above 55%,Above 65%</item>
    </array>
</resources>
